Loading index and model (first call may take ~30 s) ...
Ready ΓÇö 3029 vectors indexed across 646 documents.

 Question: What are the main risks of AI identified in these documents?

  Retrieved from docs: ['432', '1385', '1052', '467', '757']
 Answer:
The main risks of AI identified in these documents are:

* Algorithmic bias, inconsistent performance, inaccurate outputs, and other known AI failure modes (Document 1385)
* Threats to analytic integrity when employing AI tools (Document 1385)
* Risks posed by a lack of safeguards that protect human rights, civil rights, civil liberties, privacy, and other democratic values (Document 1385)
* The risk of developer bias with respect to AI (Document 432)
* Risks that the use by the Federal Government of AI, including by using AI to engage in censorship and conduct surveillance, poses to the First and Fourth Amendments to the Constitution of the United States (Document 432)
* Potential benefits and risks posed by AI, including any potential benefits and risks posed to the Federal Government (Document 467)
* Making an AI system available for use, knowing, or being reckless as to whether, it is likely to cause serious harm or substantial damage to property (Document 1052)
* Making an AI system available for use with intent to defraud the public and to cause substantial economic loss to an individual (Document 1052)

These risks are identified in various documents, including Document 1385, Document 432, Document 467, and Document 1052.
